This time,
the book is divided into two volumes.
There are 3,000 copies in total.
They have been delivered to the warehouse.
Don't mind me.
Have a meal first.
The book is not going anywhere.
Leave me alone.
Why are you haunting me?
I...
I didn't do anything.
Right, my dear?
You've made up?
No, no.
If I had known this,
I would have gone shopping with Qi.
Leave now if you want to.
I'm sick of you.
Princess,
Yikeba has indeed received a batch of silver ingots
from the Yun State.
They have been sent to the minting tribe.
Send someone over immediately.
Make sure to catch them with the evidence.
Yes.
Can't the silver ingots from Yun State
be transported to Langyue?
Yes, it can.
But it must go through the customs,
informing of its origin and purpose.
This batch of silver
entered Langyue by bypassing patrols.
Mr. Su, pay more attention when escorting in the future.
I'll take my leave.
Is it from the Fuyun Escort Agency?
You know the answer.
Who else would dare to escort goods
to the Langyue?
It was Yikeba
who killed his father.
My father and I never figured out why.
Now it seems
he has been secretly amassing Langyue's wealth,
colluding with traitors from the Yun State
to plot something.
That's why he killed the general,
to make it easier for them to smuggle money.
So,
my mother died because of them too?
Over the years,
as long as it wasn't escorted by the Fuyun Escort Agency,
other escort teams would be robbed from time to time.
But this time we came smoothly,
and we weren't robbed.
Because they were robbed too.
What do you mean?
You want to use my book as a cover,
and the Su's Escort Agency as a start,
to promote trade between the two countries?
Not a cover.
Your book is just a microcosm.
Many things from Yun Country are also needed in Langyue.
Many products from Langyue are also scarce in Yun Country.
It has been controlled by that force for too long.
It's time for a change.
Do you think
the money that Fu Xiang gave to Lang Yue
could be from the Grand Preceptor?
It's very possible.
Think about it,
in the entire Yunjing,
who else could afford
to spend so much money at once?
And according to them,
this has been going on for many years.
Is it dangerous for us
to face him directly?
What?
Are you afraid, Mr. Su?
Yes.
What are you afraid of?
I'm just thinking
we need to hire more people.
We'd better think about
how to sleep tonight.
It's unreasonable to let a woman sleep on the ground.
If my father finds out,
he'll beat me to death.
You said the same thing on the first day.
You still remember?
Don't you remember, too?
Then let's stick to the old routine.
So when can we
change this rule?
Go to sleep.
My lady, come on,
Have breakfast.
Why did you get up so early today?
Don't mention it.
I was dragged out by my brother in the morning.
Your brother
can't wait to give the whole city
to Tang Xin.
He's gone shopping again.
If I go shopping,
I just want to go with you.
So I brought you breakfast.
Come on, eat it while it's hot.
I haven't eaten either.
Give me some.
What do you want to eat?
I'll buy it for you.
No need.
After eating, I'll take Cheng Qi to the street
to let him feel the charm of Langyue.
Then I can write some stories about Langyue in the book.
And write me in it.
I need to borrow your husband for a moment.
What's going on with you two?
I wanted to ask you yesterday,
have you become a general?
Not yet.
I've always wanted to kill Yikeba,
but Princess Youzhen thinks the timing isn't right.
What about your marriage?
I entered the barracks as the emperor's son-in-law,
so I have to go through the motions.
You don't like the princess?
She trusts me a lot
and helped me find
lost martial arts classics and military books.
I'm not talking about gratitude, but affection.
What are you talking about?
Look at our rouge.
How does it compare to yours?
Shopkeeper,
could you bring more rouge?
I'd like to see more.
Princess,
what's this act all about?
What do you want to say?
Playing hard to get.
I find he is very stubborn,
stupid,
and dumb.
I'll see how long he can hold on.
What are you going to do?
Which one do you think suits me?
Your Highness
is born pretty.
I think any rouge
would suit you.
Really?
Then I'll take them all.
Princess,
you've bought so many of my books.
How about I give you the rouge for free?
Shopkeeper,
I'll take one of each
rouge here.
and send them to the Moonlight Pavilion.
You want to buy rouge?
You buy her some.
I don't need rouge.
Come on, let's go have some fun.
We are good at archery.
So we have the Qianjie Tree.
As long as you shoot the knots,
you can get a gift for your loved one.
What a good shot! Amazing!
Yeah.
I didn't know
you're such a good archer.
I want that.
This is for you.
You have a good taste.
This bag suits Cheng Qi very well.
This gift
is so precious.
You...
Yeah.
It's so precious.
I must
write you in the next novel.
I won't let you down.
Do you have a gift for me?
But I've never shot arrows.
You can try today.
OK.
I'm willing
to try for you today.
Your Royal Highness,
could my wife take your place?
What are you doing?
I'm teaching him
that the arrow
should be aligned with the target.
Good.
Give me the knot.
Since you gave a gift,
I should give one too.
The rules of Langyue state
that knots are not to be exchanged,
but given directly
to the one in your heart.
It seems my husband has someone else in mind.
In that case,
let's just call off the engagement.
Princess,
I'm not feeling well.
We can talk about the other things later.
My husband is not feeling well.
I need to check on him.
The act just now by Princess Youzhen
was to make Bai Yanli express his feelings.
After all, they are about to get married.
My lady, please don't mind.
I know.
I think Bai is sincere to Yigu.
I can tell.
My little wood finally got it.
You know what?
Pax looks handsome
in Lang Yue's clothes.
Not bad.
When Pax gave me the knot,
I didn't dare to look at him.
I felt my heart was in a mess.
When Princess gave me the wine bag,
I didn't feel anything.
When Pax left,
he seemed to look at me.
So cute.
Su Yuejiao,
I'm angry.
You always call him by his name,
but you never call me by mine.
Are you jealous?
I'm not.
Why is Bai such a good archer?
I'm jealous.
I'm really jealous.
You admit it.
Qi.
Good for you, my wife.
You've learned to manipulate me.
Learned and applied immediately.
You are influenced by those around you.
You're right.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come again next time.
Take it.
I want that one.
Thank you.
This is rouge from Astana.
It used to be tribute to the emperor.
Really?
I'll buy some for Xin.
I don't need rouge.
Don't waste money.
You can keep it as a souvenir of Astana.
What do I need a souvenir for?
People buy souvenirs after they've been there.
Don't use this excuse to buy things.
It's not easy to come here.
Are you happy?
Xin uses rouge.
When your books are sold in Astana,
I'll buy some there.
Otherwise, who knows if you're tricking me again?
You said your books are a Ning'an specialty.
I won't be fooled a second time.
I'll have to think carefully
about my next novel.
I'll try to sell it in more places,
so that my specialty can be everywhere.
Come on.
I specially asked the kitchen to prepare
the specialties of our Langyue.
Thank you for your hospitality.
It's very kind of you.
Let me introduce.
This is a naan.
The more you chew, the more delicious it is.
This is mutton flake.
It's fresh and not muttony.
This is Langyue Wine.
It's not as strong as your liquor in Yunjing.
But it's tasty and easy to drink.
It's tasty and easy to drink.
You know what I mean?
Princess,
but my wife
can't drink.
You may not know the custom of Langyue.
If the guest doesn't drink,
the host won't pour the wine.
If the guest drinks up, the host will be happy.
I know a little about it.
If the guest gets drunk,
he will be honest.
But my wife
can't drink.
She can't hold her liquor.
Who can't hold liquor?
I just don't drink often.
Don't spoil the Princess's mood.
Come on.
Drink until we're drunk.
Drink.
Cheers.
Come on.
Brother Bai.
♪A wide river.♪
♪Let's drink up.♪
Come on.
Su Yuejiao,
the guest must be drunk,
or the host will be ashamed.
Come on, cheers.
My dear, have some dishes.
My dear, have some naan.
I'll have the naan.
My dear, this naan is really delicious.
It's just a bit hard on the teeth.
Too hard.
Right, Bai?
No.
I think it's fine.
Yeah, the cake is not as hard as you.
You like me, but you don't admit it.
Who likes you?
You just don't admit it.
You coward.
Who's a coward?
I like you.
Princess, my wife is drunk.
I'll take her home. Goodbye.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
If you're not a coward,
say it again.
I like you.
You've said it to others.
Only you.
My dear,
You're drunk.
Go to bed early.
Cheng Qi.
I...
I have a lot to tell you.
Then say it.
From now on,
you should only love me,
and cherish me.
You can't lie to me,
Don't hurt me.
Don't despise me.
Discuss everything with me.
And then...
And then what?
Yeah.
And then you have to believe that
I will share weal and woe with you.
I will be with you
through thick and thin.
You can't dislike me.
You always have to feel that
I look good
even in the escort's uniform.
I promise you.
I will only love you,
protect you,
and cherish you.
My wife is unique.
Even in the escort's uniform,
you are still dazzling.
No woman in this world
can compare to you.
I'll be responsible for you.
My dear,
can we
change the rules?
I'll sleep on the ground.
No, no, no.
It's cold on the ground.
I mean,
can I sleep with you?
Fine.
Then let's sleep together.
Bro, let's sleep on the ground.
I'm coming, my dear.
What are you doing?
Didn't expect that, huh?
I didn't expect
to come back so soon.
My lady,
let me drive the carriage for you.
Stop it. I need to go back quickly.
You may feel dizzy
on the bumpy road.
Alright, my wife.
Can you be more low-key?
We're not married yet.
My wife,
didn't you say you'd be responsible for me?
Don't you go back on your words.
What?
Brother,
it's not what you think.
Su Yuejiao, Cheng Qi.
Why are you here?
To see you off.
Su Yuejiao.
I'm a stubborn person,
with a straightforward and stupid nature.
Your mother once saved me.
I wanted to repay the favor,
but ended up causing you a lot of trouble.
You finally realized it.
You almost killed me.
Cheng Qi,
I'm sorry.
I was too reckless and hurt you.
Now life has a new beginning.
It's time to get married.
When are you going back to Langyue?
Tomorrow.
Brother Bai,
from now on,
we are brothers in trouble.
What are you talking about?
Say something auspicious.
Then I wish you two...
Then I wish you two a happy marriage,
a long and harmonious life,
a perfect match,
and a life of happiness together.
Yes, that's what I want to say.
It's getting late, my dear.
We should go home.
Princess, Prince Consort,
it's a long journey.
We'll say goodbye here.
Farewell.
Safe travels.
See you soon.
Let's go.
Go.
I will personally visit you in Yunjing.
Eat up.
Come on, Xin.
Come on.
My Lord,
you look radiant
after coming back from Klak City.
Did something good happen to you?
I tell you,
there are all kinds of goods in Klak City.
If they are brought to Yunjing,
I don't know how many people will scramble to buy them.
If we can trade,
our escort agency would be prosperous.
My Lord,
apart from these,
is there anything else?
Anything else?
What else?
I heard that
the Langyue Liquor
is tasty and easy to drink.
Cheng Qi,
have you tried it?
Grandpa,
this wine is indeed good.
Just a sip,
and I'm satisfied.
I have a feeling,
I'm
about to have a great-grandchild.
Grandpa, why do you talk about this
during a meal?
Qi,
right?
I'll try.
Grandpa, you're being naughty.
Don't talk to him.
Cheng Qi,
is the ground uncomfortable to sleep on?
Actually,
sleeping on the ground can catch a cold,
but sleeping in bed
I'll be beaten.
Dad.
You can't be biased.
Pay more attention to me.
Zhen.
You founded the Escort Agency.
Yu made it grow and thrive.
I'm about to become a great-grandfather.
You must be very happy.
Zhen.
This...
What...
Dad.
What happened to you?
Where are the family members?
They all left.
This house
will no longer be owned by the Fu family.
Dad.
Is it the Grand Preceptor?
The Langyue people didn't accept the escort.
The Grand Preceptor asked the agency
to fill the blank and robbed us.
Dad,
we worked so hard for the Grand Preceptor,
but in the end, he even took our house.
They are too cruel.
I'll fight with them.
Go to the Grand Preceptor's house to make trouble.
You want to die?
Dad, I'm not stupid.
He doesn't let us live,
he can't sleep well, either.
The father and son of the Fuyun Escort Agency
committed suicide at home.
Your Majesty,
I think
they are impatient
and start to cut off their own meridians.
They also feel the crisis is coming.
Should we investigate the Grand Preceptor?
No hurry, wait a little longer.
We should get news from Langyue soon.
When the plot is fully exposed,
we can take them down.
Before that,
everything should remain as usual.
We must not act too hastily
and alert them.
Since they have made their appearance,
let's accompany them
through the final act.
Understood.
I will go and make the arrangements now.